cpmonly.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy - CPM Only

CPMonly for over 4 years has been delivering high quality results and unmatched customer service for both website publishers and advertisers. Through the years we have developed from a small group of niche sites to having relationships with 250+ site owners. We pride ourselves in lending value to our customers through efficient service, hard work, and the ability to achieve goals. It is critical to CPMonly that consumers’ privacy, rights and choices are maintained during this entire process of finding and delivering ads to consumers.

This document is intended to inform consumers how CPMonly collects, maintains and processes information we collect in the delivery of our network advertising services.

 **What types of data does CPMonly collect?**  
Inside the CPMonly network, we collect non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) such as web sites visited, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with advertiser websites, IP addresses, search terms used, and other click and browsing behavior. Additionally, we may collect non-PII technical information including IP address, OS, browser type, language settings.

 **How does CPMonly track consumer behavior?**  
Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer that allow sites to recognize the computer when you revisit the site. Generally, sites use this cookie to provide services such as auto login, information delivery, and to better understand how you are interacting with the site. These cookies enable sites to customize the site to your needs and interests, so that they can be as valuable and relevant to you as possible.

Like many websites, CPMonly sets a cookie on your computer containing an anonymous identifier. This cookie allows CPMonly to better target and analyze consumer behavior with the goal of providing better and more relevant advertising.

You are always free to decline cookies, but by doing so you may not be able to use certain features on the websites or take full advantage of all the website offerings and targeted advertising. You can always configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, erase cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Please note that if you buy a new computer, upgrade or change Web browsers or delete this “opt out” cookie, you will need to perform this process again.

 **How does CPMonly use this information?**  
CPMonly licenses the Appnexus ad serving technology to create data segments on any consumer information to create anonymous consumer segments. For example, consumers that demonstrate car buying behaviors are grouped into an auto/car-buying segments. These segments will be used to target and optimize advertiser campaigns.

CPMonly will never use this information to identify, locate or contact consumers.  
**  
Which data do we retain and for how long?**  
We maintain non-PII information on consumer behavior for 120 days. This data includes web sites visited, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with advertiser websites, IP addresses, search terms used, and other click and browsing behavior. Additionally, we may collect non-PII technical information including IP address, OS, browser type, language settings.

 **What if I have questions about how my or other consumers’ data is being used?**  
We are more than happy to respond to any customer inquiries about privacy concerns. Please contact us at NetworkCare[at]CPMonly.com with any questions or complaints.

 **The right to change this policy**  
CPMonly reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change it, we will post a link from our homepage, and possibly other highly visible places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

Privacy policy regarding information collected on the CPMonly website:

 **Personal information**  
The personal information that is collected on the CPMonly.com website is only used to contact you in regards to inquires made by you at the time of your request. Personal information is not stored nor distributed in any other manner. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.  
**  
Tracking**  
While on the CPMonly.com website we do not use cookies to track your usage in a personally identifiable way. We may use cookies to collect standard information found in a website log file such as IP address, web browser version, etc, but we never attempt to match this information to your personally identifiable information.

 **Additional information disclosures**  
We reserve the right to disclose information we have collected from you if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our employees, customers, or the public.

 **Linking to other sites**  
A link from the CPMonly web site to another web site does not imply our endorsement of that site. We do not control the sites to which we link and assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Therefore, you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any sites you access from our site.

 **Contact us**  
If you have any question about our site, company or service, you should first consult our website. This site includes links to company information, answers to frequently asked questions, and all of CPMonly’s current policies. If you have further questions or any concerns or complaints about how your personal information is used, please contact us.  
**  
Correcting/updating/deleting/deactivating personal information**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by contacting support on our contact us page.

 **Security**  
CPMonly uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your information. CPMonly treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. Only authorized administrators have password-protected access to our data and we routinely review our security logs and perform regular security audits.

Dakine Media LLC (DBA: CPMonly)  
8620 N. New Braunfels, Suite #424, San Antonio, TX 78217  
347.470.9504

This policy was last updated on June 28th, 2011.
